[
	{
		"type": "mc",
		"question": "The Vancouver Canucks are named for Johnny Canuck. Who was he?",
		"option":{
			"0": "A political cartoon character",
			"1": "A canadian explorer",
			"2": "One of vancouver’s most famous hockey players",
			"3": "One of vancouver’s first settlers"
			},
		"answer": "0"
	},

	{
		"type": "mc",
		"question": "Vancouver Canucks joined NHL in:",
		"option":{
			"0": "1955",
			"1": "1960",
			"2": "1965",
			"3": "1970"
			},
		"answer": "3"
	},

	{
		"type": "mc",
		"question": "Which NBA player own lots of his own brand’s gym in vancouver?",
		"option":{
			"0": " Kobe Bryant",
			"1": " Steve Nash",
			"2": " Lebron James",
			"3": "Tony Parker"
			},
		"answer": "1"
	},

	{
		"type": "mc",
		"question": "Which place is one of the skiing/snowboarding place in vancouver?",
		"option":{
			"0": "Whistler",
			"1": "Grouse ",
			"2": "Cypress",
			"3": "The Big White"
			},
		"answer": "0"
	},

	{
		"type": "mc",
		"question": "You can do the following activities for free on Christmas Day in robson square:",
		"option":{
			"0": "Skating",
			"1": "Hockey",
			"2": "Street dancing lesson",
			"3": "Yoga Lesson"
			},
		"answer": "0"
	},

	{
		"type": "fill",
		"question": "_______ is renowned for its scenery and has one of the largest urban parks in North America.",
		"answer": "Stanley Park"
	},

	{
		"type": "mc",
		"question": "Vancouver Whitecaps FC is a local team for what sport activity?",
		"option":{
			"0": "Football",
			"1": "Hockey",
			"2": "Baseball",
			"3": "Soccers"
			},
		"answer": "3"
	},

	{
		"type": "mc",
		"question": "When was the Canucks established?",
		"option":{
			"0": "1945",
			"1": "1955",
			"2": "1965",
			"3": "1975"
			},
		"answer": "0"
	},

	{
		"type": "check",
		"question": "Which sports team are in Vancouver?",
		"option":{
			"0": "BC Lions",
			"1": "Whitecaps FC",
			"2": "Giant",
			"3": "Canucks"			
			},
		"answer": "0,1,2,3"
	},

	


	{
		"type": "fill",
		"question": "Vancouver Stanley Cup riot happened in the year of _______.",
		"answer": "2011"
	},


	{
		"type": "fill",
		"question": "Vancouver hosted the winter Olympic festival in the year of _______ .",
		"answer": "2010"
	}
]